Contact

gilsonpcf@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/gilsonpcf (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Educação

Treinamento e desenvolvimento Tecnologias educacionais

Languages

Portuguese (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

Gilson Pereira do Carmo Filho

Computer Scientist | Software Engineer | Professor Fortaleza

Summary

Extensive experience in Computer Science, with emphasis on computer methodologies and techniques, working mainly in the following specialties: Software Engineering, Databases, and Information Systems. Experience of twenty-five years in large software development and maintenance projects, involving important public and private institutions. Solid experience in team leadership, project management, and business processes.

Experience

Universidade de Fortaleza Professor August 2014 - Present (8 years) Fortaleza

Center of Technological Sciences

GP Tecnologia em Sistema de Ensino Managing Partner March 2011 - Present (11 years 5 months) Fortaleza

Universidade Federal do Ceará 1 year 8 months

Project Manager
January 2012 - April 2013 (1 year 4 months)
Fortaleza

R&D Laboratory in Design and Mobile Computing Department of Computer Science

Substitute Professor September 2011 - December 2011 (4 months) Fortaleza

Department of Information Sciences

Techne Engenharia e Sistemas

13 years 6 months

Project Manager

February 2008 - February 2011 (3 years 1 month)

Fortaleza

Systems Analyst

September 1997 - January 2008 (10 years 5 months)

Fortaleza

Universidade Federal do Ceará Substitute Professor August 2005 - July 2007 (2 years)

Fortaleza

Department of Computer Science

Education

Universidade Federal do Ceará

M.Sc., Teleinformatics Engineering · (2005 - 2006)

FGV - Fundação Getulio Vargas

MBA, Project Management, Project Management · (2008 - 2010)

Universidade Federal do Ceará

B.Sc., Computer Science · (1991 - 1994)